<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Eamonn Cottrell</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Eamonn Cottrell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:49:06 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 13:11:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/hugo/</guid>
      <description>This past week, I&amp;rsquo;ve put together my first legit theme for Hugo, and it&amp;rsquo;s for a pretty niche audience: recovery groups.
The Problem: Recovery Groups are Still on Dial Up Most groups are in the stone age when it comes to technology. If they do have a page, it&amp;rsquo;s something that looks terrible, was made a century ago, and is no longer maintained.
Groups have regular literature and liturgy that circulates for participation in every meeting&amp;ndash;often occurring many times through the week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recursion</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/recursion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 13:52:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/recursion/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not a genius, but I have managed to accumulate a fair amount of know-how about a lot of things from specialty coffee to writing fiction to web development.
One of the problems I run into when I&amp;rsquo;m diving into a new (or old) subject is my seeming inability to stop prodding at its underlying roots.
When looking for a TV series to watch, I become lost in a rabbit hole of browser tabs, backstories and articles on the proper way to consume content that was intended to simply be entertaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web3</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/web3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 12:18:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/web3/</guid>
      <description>A Little Late I&amp;rsquo;m one of the dumb ones.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the know regarding Bitcoin and blockchain and the next wave of the internet (Web3) for many years. I just haven&amp;rsquo;t paid it any attention.
Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting curious again, and I decided to take a quick course after stumbling across a relatively new ed-tech company, _buildspace.
They&amp;rsquo;re a YCombinator company, and pivoted from earlier educational ideas under the name ZipSchool to land on the Web3 space.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
