<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Podcasts on Eamonn Cottrell</title>
    <link>http://example.org/podcasts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Podcasts on Eamonn Cottrell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:51:49 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/podcasts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Re Verse</title>
      <link>http://example.org/podcasts/re-verse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:04:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/podcasts/re-verse/</guid>
      <description>re-verse is an evolution in progress. A swelling undercurrent of short scriptures brought to life in a musical podcast which hopes to breach your ears with both comfort and insecurity. With truth and fear. With cautious optimism and with plenty of dissonance. Re-verse hopes to be a remedy for the wishy-washy-feel goodness of what seems to be a modern misrepresentation of the gospel of truth which I believe holds power. Re-verse hopes to capture moments in time through music with scripture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sieis Soundtracks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/podcasts/sieis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 14:50:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/podcasts/sieis/</guid>
      <description>Sieis Soundtracks is a collection of ephemeral soundtracks. It spawned in 2011 from the longer form fna show. Inspriation came orgiainlly from NIN&amp;rsquo;s phenomenal Ghosts I-IV album. The original 37 episodes of Sieis were re-released in 2019 across four 10-track seasons, and additional seasons will be release in this 10-track format going forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fna Show</title>
      <link>http://example.org/podcasts/fna_show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 13:32:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/podcasts/fna_show/</guid>
      <description>The fna show is an aural excursion. an experiment in sound and idea.
The crucifixion of complacency continues to be the driving force behind the fna show. The fna show began as a haphazard effort towards a comedy podcast back in 2006. It was an excuse to record a group of friends while talking about absolutely nothing. It evolved over the first dozen episodes into a musical meandering weaving through scripted content varying from poems to rants to short stories.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
